# Jennifer N Hedgcock



linkedin.com/in/jhedgcock



http://www.hi-jennifer.com



jennifernhf@gmail.com



5204002622

# Summary

Front End Web Developer with a customer service background and over 4 years of experience helping clients to bridge the gap between tech and marketing.

Experience with HTML, CSS/SCSS/, Javascript, jQuery, CMS, React.js, Vue.js, templating engines (Handlebars, Freemarker, Jinja), build tools and task runners (Webpack, NPM, Gulp, Grunt) and version control (Git, Mercurial).

# **Experience**



# CRESCENDO Front-End Web Developer

Crescendo Collective

Feb 2016 - Mar 2020 (4 years 2 months)

Interacted daily with client-led and internal teams, including offshore QA teams

Programmed enterprise-level webapps, microsites and marketing tools

Integrated front-end with Magnolia CMS and Java backend

Led daily/weekly releases and deployment processes

Created documentation for both clients and internal teams



## **Spanish Tutor**

Wyzant

Jan 2015 - Dec 2015 (1 year)

#### Weights & Measures Lab Assistant

GIA (Gemological Institute of America)

Jul 2013 - Aug 2014 (1 year 2 months)

Processed 400+ stones daily using proprietary diagnostic technologies

Supported research team to develop and test diagnostic technologies, and project initiatives.



#### 🚺 Student Advisor

Jones International University

Feb 2012 - Nov 2012 (10 months)

Assisted students with on-boarding procedures

Maintained successful student retention rates

Mentored students on academic and work-life success strategies

### Education



### MiraCosta College

Associate's Degree, Web Development & Design 2014 - 2015



### M University of Arizona

Bachelor's degree, Latin American Studies | Political Science

2003 - 2007